so
[Music]
salutations it is a little after 7 a.m
and i'm enjoying a rare warm spring
morning
i've been trying to put some changes
into my day recently in order to add
more meaning to my life outside of a
busy work schedule
which can feel so consuming at times
i like to consider my daily routine as
more of a practice instead of something
scheduled out
to have a routine sounds like something
that you aren't supposed to break
while a daily practice is something that
evolves and develops over time
it isn't about doing things a certain
way it's about learning what we need as
we go through the process of living well
[Music]
for me an overly rigid structure to my
mornings makes me feel as if everything
i'm trying to do in order to prepare for
the day is for the sole purpose of being
productive and efficient and having high
energy
no doubt these things are necessary at
times and can be very beneficial but
i've also found a lot of fulfillment in
bending those rules and allowing things
into my routine that are just there for
pure enjoyment or even
dare i say and to waste a little time in
the best ways i could imagine
reading a story
daydreaming taking a walk
sipping tea
we focus so much on making every minute
count towards a goal and it is so
liberating to have the goal to be
enjoying that minute
[Music]
so
my
[Music]
it's been a very long time since i kind
of just really gave my all into enjoying
some kind of
frivolous hobby for lack of a better
word and
i actually went to my local specialty
market and
went and spent a long time smelling all
the different types of teas
and seeing what kinds they had i've
really enjoyed the process it's actually
was meaningful because i thought
you know
when as adults do we really
prioritize taking at least
a few minutes if not a little part of
the day
now and then to just have fun speaks to
that inner child and i had just so much
fun picking out tea and so that's what
i decided i would do today
that i would take a little bit of time
between work breaks
to
organize some of it and put it away
[Music]
do
so
[Music]
do
it was so fruitful to add some new
things to my routine and to see how
they felt and to be honest i found that
i think the answer isn't to copy other
people's routines necessarily
or to just
bring in something that people say would
be helpful in just doing it it really is
listening to yourself and seeing what
you enjoy to do you know i like getting
up early-ish but i will never be one of
those people that wake up at 5am i
i just it doesn't work for me and it
doesn't
add to my day another thing that i do is
that
i enjoy journaling but i actually really
enjoy painting
and that is one way that i'm able to
communicate my thoughts and feelings
about the day
in color and in paint and i
found that prioritizing some time for
that was actually benefiting me more
than putting a little time aside for my
journal so
it's just so interesting to
realize you know just to listen to
yourself and find find what works
sending all of you my love
i will see you very soon
take care of yourselves
and
i'm gonna go on a walk because i've not
yet gone on a walk today and my puppy is
very excited and i heard a little fairy
told me
that there is a field of blue bells up
the road and
i am
really excited to go see if that dream
is a reality so
i will take you along but that being
said
have a wonderful week goodbye
[Music]
i decided to adventure up this
random little road
and i wasn't expecting to find too much
because this is where all the fires went
through so much life is here and it's
blooming and it's beautiful and abundant
and
it's just such a beautiful reminder to
me at least that
no matter how much destruction can
happen there's always
always the opportunity to bring back
so much and
for
beauty to grow again and for
gosh it just feels like
if
if wildfires can tear through an entire
valley and
the very next year a field of blue bells
is here
and then anything anything is possible
it is just
it is just so beautiful
[Music]
oh
hello
thank you again all of you for all your
kindness and support it has really been
such an important part this week in
trying to rethink how i
spend free time when i do have it i
don't have a lot of it but when i do
have it even if it's just a couple
minutes
to just stop for a few seconds and to
just
look up and turn my face to the sky and
absorb that
light the sunshine and just and just
look
and just see wow
if i'm sounding like a fanciful fairy
right now it's because i i definitely
feel like one i'm feeling very wonderful
today
and it is giving me courage to face the
weak and face work and responsibilities
and all these fears with with new
enthusiasm i did think that i would
answer at least just a couple questions
um
a surprising amount of people were
wondering
um if i was gonna go on a honeymoon and
i i thought that was really
funny because i haven't even thought
about whether or not i'm gonna go on a
honeymoon since i'm getting married this
may
and um after the whole process of
purchasing a home it just really isn't
something feasible or practical for us
to do right now i don't think it would
be a very smart decision
um and
we would love to take a very short trip
somewhere i would love to go to
canada because i actually have not
explored canada very much
i have been there multiple times but i
would love to
go back to one of my very favorite
places which was prince edward island i
went over there when i was 15 years old
it was
a very special gift
that my father gave me because when you
are 15 in hispanic culture you celebrate
your quinceanera
and that
quinceanera is kind of like a sweet 16
but it
has this added meaning of not only are
you
you know becoming an adult
but you are entering adult society and
you have a new level of kind of
responsibility and it's it's a very
uh usually a very huge party but my
introverted self did not want to party
so my father was kind enough to
compromise
prince edward island
is the home of lucy maud montgomery and
she wrote the anne of green gables books
and i was absolutely obsessed with the
end of green gables books when i was
much younger so i was able to go over
there and see the museums
and see some plays and really fall in
love
with that very unique very special
little island i would love to visit
again so that is another option
potentially for a future honeymoon when
we are in a different place financially
for sure we would love to go there
perhaps
over here as well the summers are kind
of a gamble sometimes they're going to
be beautiful and incredible and you can
get out into the mountains and go
camping
and other years
the entire sky is filled with smoke from
wildfires and
you know you are quite limited in what
you can do and so
we're kind of waiting to see also what
the summer's going to look like because
a beautiful clear summer without the
smoke pollution is very special and we
wouldn't want to miss that
if that is how it ends up being so
um yeah so we will see what we end up
doing i am um
very excited for the future
i'm feeling better i think it takes time
to
recover from life burnout so every year
i collect kind of a little uh bowl full
of spring beauties and i
love to find a really abundant field and
just collect some for a very special
meal and then it is just so wonderful to
come back the next year and just see
it's so abundant and it really motivates
you to learn about the plants in your
area
learn how to
mindfully forage it is also such a
beautiful way to connect with nature and
be reminded that we can create a
beautiful working relationship with it
it's up to us and we can we can really
do it almost anytime we can start
learning and
connecting and
finding out incredible
unusual things like corms of spring
beauties taste
like the most incredible
floral infused potatoes i've ever tasted
it was absolutely delicious and i just
couldn't believe how wonderful they were
because usually when i forage
i have to be more open-minded to unusual
flavors these were just felt such cozy
comfort food type flavor that i really
really enjoyed it and
yeah it's just so wonderful to just have
a little special treat and then you get
to be excited for next year to have that
treat again it's a lot like
morel mushrooms
i'm sending all of you my love
and i will see you very soon
[Music]
you